You do what’s best for the family.
Fresh Kills is a drama, crime film directed by Jennifer Esposito.
Rose Larusso, an inquisitive young girl in 1980s Staten Island,
discovers her father is an emerging mafia kingpin.
Rose's growing desire to break free from the path set before her soon threatens her existence and alienates
her from her closest allies: her mother Francine, her sister Connie, and her aunt Christine.
Rose, played by Emily Bader.
Connie, played by Odessa A'zion.
Francine Larusso, played by Jennifer Esposito.
Joe Larusso, played by Domenick Lombardozzi.
Christine, played by Annabella Sciorra.
Allie, played by Nicholas Cirillo.
Fresh Kills is a 2023 American drama film marking the directorial debut
of Jennifer Esposito, who also wrote and co-produced it.
The film stars Esposito, Emily Bader, Odessa A'zion, Domenick
Lombardozzi, Nicholas Cirillo and Annabella Sciorra.
Fresh Kills was released in the United States on June 14, 2024.
The tone is emotional.